本字幕由 PTT同志影视作品板 2013重新校稿
原字幕取自网路资源  仅供学习 禁用任何商业盈利行为
校稿： Aaa　　　最後校稿：mohiwa
同志亦凡人 Queer As Folk S01E06
好吧  我是个崇拜超级英雄的同志
Okay, so i'm a gay man with a superhero fetish.
是的  的确有我们这种人    不过
Yes, we're out there. And no, it doesn't
我们并不是不成熟
Have anything to do with immaturity.
我认为我们同志们能从漫画书里
I think we gay boys learn important
学到很多东西
Lessons from comic books.
第一  世界上有很多坏人
One, there are a lot of villains out there,
所以你最好拥有几样秘密超能力
So you better develop some secret powers.
第二  你想穿紧身衣  你身材要够好
Two, if you have a good body, you can wear tight clothes.
第三  最好是有个跟班或夥伴一起行动　(例如蝙蝠侠和罗宾)
And, three it's always good to be part of a dynamic duo.
我完全的搞砸了
I totally blew it.
放心  外面还有很多怪叔叔
Don't worry. There's still plenty of creepy old
等着要上你
Who'd love to get in your pants.
他没那麽老
He wasn't that old.
他也没那麽怪   他很棒   可是我第一次跟医生约会
He wasn't creepy. He was nice. My first doctor.
-理疗师而已　　 -也算是医生… 我想是吧
-Chiropractor.   -That counts... I think.
新的《猫女》出刊罗
Uh, we got in the new catwoman.
酷
Cool.
他带我去一间很不错的餐厅
He takes me to this really nice restaurant,
我却像个傻屌
And I behave like a fucking idiot,
打扮得油里油气的傻屌
Dressed up like some slick asshole.
嘿   那件皮夹克可是花了我三万六
Hey, that was my $1,200 leather jacket.
那不适合我的型
It wasn't me.
你知道吗?
You know why?
因为我什麽咖都不是...
'Cause I'm nobody. That's my problem.
你到底有没有听我说话?
Are you even listening to me?
这些自怨自怜的话我会自动消音　我没"性"趣
I tune out self-pity. It makes my dick soft.
我们可不想失去"性"趣...
And we wouldn't want that...
是吧
Would we?
就当我刚才什麽都没说
Just forget I said anything.
喔 你看
Oh, wow. Look.
新的幻影女杀手公仔　 (《夜魔侠》漫画的反派)
It's the new electra woman doll.
我买这个给盖斯
I'm going to buy this for Gus.
不要   我不想要他变成同志少年
Don't. I don't want a gay kid.
两个拉拉在抚养他
He's being raised by two lesbians.
他需要一些女人味的东西
He's going to need a feminine influence.
况且   这个当收藏品也不错
Besides, it'll be a collector's item.
我拿去吧   我等下要去她们家
I'll take it. I'm going over there.
我也要去  不行
I'll go too.  No.
你回去找那个医生
You're going back to the doctor.
叫他再给你一次机会
Tell him you want to give it another try.
你妈妈知道你跑出来买首饰吗?
Does your mom know you're out buying jewelry?
她什麽都不管的
Oh, she's totally cool with everything.
至少她假装不管我  因为她害怕
Or at least she's pretending to be because she's scared
-我会离家出走 然後去当发型师　　　　　-我恨你
-I'll run away and become a hairdresser.  -I hate you.
我都还没解释什麽的
My mom's such a bitch, and I haven't
我妈就开始噜嗦一大堆了
Even given her a reason yet.
-这个如何?　　　　　-基味十足
-How about these?   -They're totally queer.
闭嘴　　这是我们友情的象徵
Shut up. They're a symbol of our friendship.
好吧  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
事实上　我没带钱
Actually, I don't have any money.
我得存钱买假身份证
I had to buy a new fake i.d.
你看  是她们
Look! That's them!
布莱恩的拉拉朋友
Brian's lesbians.
嘿  你们好
Hey! Hey, How's it going?
不好意思  我们认识吗?   我是贾斯汀
I'm sorry. Do we know you?   I'm justin.
布莱恩的朋友
Brian's friend.
盖斯出生那晚我在场   我还帮忙决定他的名字
I was there the night Gus was born. I named him.
哦  是的
Oh, right. Yeah.
等他在加油站工作   我们还得谢谢你呢 (Gus, Gas同音)
So when Gus ends up pumping gas, we'll have you to thank.
这是达芙妮
This is Daphne.
你好  我不是拉拉    不过我很崇拜你们
Hi. I'm not a lesbian, but I-I'm a big fan.
他都长这麽大了
He's gotten so big already.
整天吃饱了就睡   你也会长得这麽大
You would too if all you did was sleep and eat all day.
的确如此    他是我见过最可爱的宝宝
He does.  He's like the cutest baby I've ever seen.
如果你需要临时保姆...
If you need a baby-sitter
除非你是认真的  不然别随口说说
Don't say that unless you mean it.
那你有什麽东西要搬到车上
And if you need any help carrying stuff to the car,
我可以帮忙
I'd be glad to be of assistance.
哇…　你还真帮得上忙呢
Wow, you're good for 1,001 uses.
我们等会见吗?    我不确定
I'll see you later?   I don't know
我不干了
I'm out.
工作吗?  太赞了
At work? That's fabulous.
我的意思是离开那些地方
Out of the scene, I mean.
我已经决定了
I've made up my mind.
不去酒吧  不去三温暖  不去夜店
No more bars, no more baths, no more clubs.
你不会在巴比伦看到我了
You'll never see my face at Babylon again.
拜托  你不能就因为那次
Oh, please! You can't let one little
一点嗑药的小意外就被击败了
Drug-induced coma get you down.
这件你觉得如何
What do you think?
你看起来很廉价
You look unbelievably trashy.
说的我心动了   买了
Talked me into it. I'll buy it.
你没听懂我的意思
You missed my point entirely.
我们做的每件事  甚至我们穿的衣服
Everything we do, even the clothes we wear,
都是有意无意地　有时还很刻意地
Is a conscious, or worse yet,
为了可以打一炮而穿成这样
Unconscious attempt to get laid.
的确   太强调"性"的部份
Yes, it's true. There is an overemphasis on sex.
为什麽不直接买小二号的衣服穿上？
But why not buy two sizes too small and go with it?
因为很不幸的   有人天生就无法这麽紧身的莱卡
Because, tragically, some of us were not born to wear lycra.
看看交友版吧
Here, check out the personals.
或许可以找到不爱外出鬼混的另一半
Perhaps you'll find someone to not go out with.
有件事  我一直搞不懂   这些广告
You know, one thing I never understood about these ads,
为什麽老写着 "舔乳头"  和 "活塞运动" 这些字眼?
Why is it always "tit work" and "ass play"?
如果你问我   这些实在很难让人.....
If you ask me, it's a lot harder to
看这个广告... 地点在同志文化中心
Hey, look at this...at the center
"佳人有约" 想跟其他的单身同志联谊
Date Bait. Meet other single gay men
共度一个高雅的交流之夜
"In a civilized evening of conversation.
不是路边钓男人   不会被当面拒绝
No pick-ups, no face-to-face rejection."
-他们有个"三十而立之夜"　　　　-在哪?  太平间吗?
-They have an over-30 night.　-Where? At the morgue?
因为你说了这句    你要跟我一起去
Just for that, you're going with me.
我又还没 30岁
I am not over 30.
那我也不会一个人去
And I am not going alone.
我不记得我们还有安排复诊时间
I didn't realize we had scheduled a follow-up visit.
是没有   我说我要挂急诊
We didn't. I told them it was an emergency.
-问题出在哪？　　　　 -出在我是个混蛋
-What's the problem? -I'm a jerk.
你能治疗这症状吗?
Can you adjust that?
有监於这不是持续性的病症
Provided it's not a permanent condition.
老实跟你说吧　  我不太跟人约会
See, the thing is, I don't date very often.
我是说  那种 "吃饭、聊天"
You know, real "eat a meal, talk,
"含情脉脉注视对方" 的传统约会
Stare into each other's eyes" kind of dates.
所以我那天有点反常
So I-I kind of freaked.
抱歉  我当时表现得像个大傻屌
And I'm sorry I was such an asshole.
你没有表现得像...  大傻屌
You weren't... an asshole.
相信我  我看过很多的傻屌..
Believe me, I've seen assholes and..
我是说...
I mean, uh..
我觉得自已很白烂
I feel shitty about it.
我真的喜欢你
And... I really like you.
我想你也许真的喜欢我
And I think you might actually have liked me.
-我真的喜欢你   -真的吗?
-I do like you.   -You do?
那你觉得我们可以重新开始吗?
Well, do you think we could start over?
坐下
Sit down.
你真的很可爱   你知道吗?
You're adorable, you know that?
我带了这个给盖斯
I got something for Gus.
太贴心了
That's so sweet.
我们等一下会打电话谢谢 "迈克"
We'll call Michael later to thank him.
你什麽时候开始学画画?
How long have you been drawing?
我还是婴儿的时候
My mom brought me crayons when I was
我妈就买了蜡笔给我   我就一直画到现在
Still in the crib. I never stopped.
他在这里干嘛?
What's he doing here?
我们在街上遇到
We ran into each other on the street.
好像是有缘份的巧遇上
It was like, this weird coincidence.
最好是
I bet.
这些画得很好
You know, these are good.
我妈也这麽说    琳赛是美术老师喔
That's what my mom says.  Lindsay's an art teacher.
以你这样的年纪
For someone your age, you have an
你对人体的掌握很到位
Amazing feel for the human form.
我也注意到了
I've noticed that myself.
-看看这张　　-别给他看
-Look at this.  -Oh, don't show him.
-你什麽时候画的?　　　　　-你睡着的时候
-When did you draw that?  -When you were asleep.
啊  割过的  跟我想的一样
Ah, circumcised. Just like I thought.
你知道吗同文中心要办场美术展
You know, there's going to be an art show at the G.L.C.
那是什麽?
What's that?
同志文化中心
The gay and lesbian center.
约不到炮的同志都躲去那里
Safe haven for fags who can't get laid.
你应该偶尔去跟
You know, it might be good to get out and
一些"年轻"的朋友交流
meet some nice young men for a change,
每年的募款活动
It's the annual fund-raiser.
茉蕾妮和我都是董事会成员
Melanie and I are on the board.
你愿不愿展出你的画?
Would you like to have your work in the show?
你是说   展示我画的东西给别人看?
You mean, people seeing my stuff?
-是的　　  -那也太…赞了
-Yeah.　　-That'd be intense.
或许...    可以吧
But... yeah.
也对  给他找点事做
Good. Give him some activity
这样他就没空再缠着我了
So he'll stop stalking me.
少自作多情了你
Don't flatter yourself.
我们喜欢贾斯汀  他可以留下来
We like Justin. Justin can stay.
我们会邀请所有人过来
We'll make sure everyone comes.
-包括你　　　　　-(Bitch)
-Including you.　 -(Bitch)
如果你对谁感兴趣  就把他的号码写下来
Write down the numbers of the men you're interested in.
如果电脑显示配对成功
And if the computer matches you up,
你们就得出去约会   这是参加规则
You have to go out on a date. Those are the rules.
大家好  我叫布鲁斯
Hi, uh, my name is Bruce.
我有点紧张   我一年前才出柜
I'm a little nervous. I only came out about a year ago.
我爱吃 Ben&Jerry牌的夹心巧克力
I like, uh, ben and jerry's chubby hubby.
我在卡内基梅隆大学教钢琴和声乐
I teach piano and voice at carnegie-mellon.
还喜欢看《欢乐一家亲》
And watching "frasier".
我朋友要我来的
My friend made me come.
我想找个有爱心  而且喜欢吉娃娃的人
I'm looking for a nice guy who likes chihuahuas.
我有三只吉娃娃
I have three.
要是让我男朋友知道   他绝对会杀了我
My boyfriend would kill me if he knew.
而且我很爱紧身小泳裤
And I have a speedo fetish.
尤其是红色和青色的
Especially red and teal.
不久前  我和一个在巴比伦遇见..
I recently, uh, went home with this...
非常帅的男孩一起回家
Very cute boy that I met at babylon.
他带了那种药
Uh, he had some drugs.
我还组织了一个本地的同志合唱团
I also conduct the local gay men's chorus.
希望你们能来出席我们的音乐会
I hope you'll all come to our upcoming concert.
我想让自己年轻一点　性感一些
I wanted to seem young and sexy
所以我就喝了它
So I took some,
结果我就陷入昏迷　  然後...
And I ended up in a coma. And, uh...
我非常希望在排练过後
And I would love someone
有个人在等我回家
To come home to after rehearsal.
而现在
Now...
我想找一段以认真交往为基础的恋情
I'm looking for a relationship based on something real.
我想这里也许有人
And I thought maybe there might be someone
和我有同样的想法
Here who's looking for the same thing.
呃   大概就这样
And, uh, that's all.
傻屌、傻屌摆满桌　没有一根我想要
Faggots, faggots everywhere and not a drop to drink.
坦白说  这里没一个人能
I can honestly say I have no desire
挑起我的性慾
To have sex with any of these people.
我也是
Me neither.
总算是有个起头吧
It's a start.
我从没见过这麽多的漫画
I've never seen so many comic books.
我带回家的每个人都这麽说
That's what everybody I bring home says.
我是说... 曾有人这样说  (怕被误会钓很多人)
I mean... people have told me that.
这个大块头是谁?
Who's the big fella?
Captain astro.
我那朋友  艾美特  他和我住一起
Um, my friend Emmett, he's staying with me.
本来是暂时性的
It was supposed to be a temporary thing
不过他有点反客为主了
But he became sort of a squatter
不好意思　他随时都有可能回来
He may come home at any time, so sorry about that.
你不用每件事都道歉的
You don't have to apologize for everything.
我知道    我常这样   抱歉
I know. I do that. I'm sorry.
想喝点什麽吗?  果汁?
Do you want anything? Juice?
啤酒?
Beer.
我没有红酒..
I don't have any wine.
慢一点
Slow.
嘿   你们想好要吃什麽了吗?
Hi, guys. You know what you'd like?
我要培根起士汉堡
I'll have the bacon cheeseburger,
中号薯条  还有百事可乐
Medium fries, and, uh, a pepsi.
好的
Okay.
嗯  我要..
Uh, I'll have the, uh,
烤鲔鱼  还有
Uh, the grilled tuna and, um... I, uh...
ㄟ  一杯水
Just... I-I'll have water.
拜托  放松一点好吗
Oh, come on. live a little.
我看得出来你亏待自己很久了
I can tell you've been denying yourself for way too long.
好吧  我点跟他一样的
All right, give me what he's having.
好的  马上就来
Okay, coming right up.
他笑起来很好看
He has a nice smile.
没有其他特别的吗
Among other attributes.
我肯定他很优秀
I'm sure he's a fine person.
我猜他拿过罗氏奖学金
Rhodes scholar would be my guess.
你知道吗  通常我会在他回来之前
You know, ordinarily I'd be wracking my brain
绞尽脑汁想一些
To come up with some
很烂的搭讪台词
Pathetic line for when he comes back.
比如  "之前没见过你，你是新来的吗？  "
Like, "I haven't seen you here before. Are you new ?"
或者  "我们之前好像在哪见过?"
Or, uh, "Do I know you from somewhere?
"没有吗?   那肯定是在梦里了"
No? Must be a dream.
"什麽时候这里开始找男模来打工了?"
"So when did they start hiring models here?"
你的比我的还烂   我该去洗手间吗?
You're worse than I am. You, um, want me to go
好让你有机会搭讪他   或是
To the men's room so you can take a crack at him, or
我的老天  省省吧　这种台词从没成功过
Oh, god no! It never worked anyway.
全是些没用的调情烂招
All that useless flirting.
跳脱那种只追求帅哥的世界
It is such a relief
真让人松了一口气
To be out of that world.
我必须跟你坦白一件事
I have a confession to make.
我去"佳人有约"
I didn't go to "date bait" just to
不只是为了多找几个人来参加
Drum up an audience
-我们第500场的桑德海姆音乐会　-我了解
-For our 500 Sondheim concert.   -I had a feeling.
我想找一个和我互相交流的人
I was hoping that I would find someone I could connect to.
-一个聊的来的人　　　　　-没错
-Someone appropriate.　-Exactly.
一个彼此适合的人
Someone appropriate.
所以
Well...
我想我们可以先了解对方  然後...
I say let's get to know each other and...
顺其自然
See what happens.
慢慢来
Take it slow.
我也喜欢慢板多过快板
I always preferred andante to presto anyway.
好了  两位
Okay, boys.
这饮料给你们降温一下
These'll help cool you down.
在我的乳头上搞了27分钟     我有计时
27 minutes on my nipples! I clocked it.
我是说  我希望他手也别闲着
I mean, I expected him to know what to do with his hands,
毕竟这是他的本职　　　(理疗师双关语)
'Cause that's his business,
不过他舌头真是超灵活的
But he has the most talented tongue.
-每一次我高潮的时候　-每一次?
-Every time I came　　-Every time ?
他都会还继续
He would just keep on going.
舔我的    每一个部位
Licking me... everywhere.
我认识一个人  他可以
I once knew a guy who could tie a cherry
用舌头把樱桃梗打结
Stem into a knot with his tongue.
我当时还有点怕他帮我口交
I was afraid to let him blow me.
27分钟?
27 minutes?
每个乳头舔13分钟半   还是...
W-was that 13 1/2 on each nipple, or...?
右边16分钟  左边11分钟
16 right, 11 left.
喔   说不定他勃起就需要这麽久
Yeah, that's probably how long it takes him to get it up.
这我不清楚
I wouldn't know.
我没看过它软下来
I never saw it when it was down.
又是一个 威尔钢 的亲身见证
Another viagra success story.
你今晚要带他去伍迪吗?
So are you bringing him to woody's tonight?
他好像不怎麽爱去酒吧
He's not really into the bar scene.
那他喜欢什麽?
Well what is he into?
他自己的生活吧
His life.
就像我现在约会的这个
Like the guy I met.
-你在跟人约会？　　　-他人很好
-You met someone?   -He's very nice.
很聪明  也很风趣
Very intelligent, very interesting.
是一号还是零号?
Is he a top or a bottom?
你知道吗   并不是所有人都跟你一样
You know, not everybody judges
看人只在乎1或0号
People by your criteria.
-罗杰和我    　 -罗杰?
-Roger and I...   -Roger?
罗杰和我已经决定
Roger and I have decided
在我们上床之前   要先好好认识彼此
To get to know each other before we have sex.
你以为你们是拉拉吗?
What do you think you are, lesbians?
像电影《越爱越美丽》(柏拉图式爱情)   我是说真的
It's like "the mirror has two faces". No, no, it is.
芭芭拉?史翠珊  演一个老处女教授
Because Barbra plays an unattractive professor,
不是要吐槽你
No offense,
剧中和  杰夫?布里奇斯结婚
Who marries Jeff Bridges
一开始他们都不热衷  享受性爱
Because neither one of them can handle sex.
当然芭芭拉是有慾望的
But of course Barbara gets horny because,
拜托  杰夫可是个天菜啊
Hello, Jeff's such a dreamboat.
所以  她站上踩步机
So, um, she hops on a stairmaster for like,
大概 2分钟吧
Two minutes,
吃了根胡萝卜棒
Eats a carrot stick and then,
然後证明她  其实可以很性感
Poof-- she gorgeous.
接着她走进房间
Then she comes in
穿得像《我要求审判》里的高级应召女
Dressed like the hooker in "nuts"
当然就引起了杰夫的性慾
And of course Jeff's willing to fuck her.
然後  他们...    就在街上跳舞
And, um, they... dance in the street.
结果她还是没被提名最佳女主角
And she still wasn't nominated.
我觉得  要嘛就来一炮  不嘛就没炮可打
You know, you do it right away, or you don't do it at all.
我替你高兴    小迈
I'm happy for you, Mikey.
他最好是
Fuck he is.
贾斯汀  达芙妮来了
Justin, daphne's here!
莫利
Molly
我们要迟到了
We're going to be late.
贾斯汀有跟我提过
Hey, look. Justin told me how great
说你对这一切都很能体谅
You're being about everthing.
我想告诉你  我觉得
And, uh, I just want to say I think
贾斯汀有你这麽善解人意的母亲  他很幸运
He's really lucky to have such an understanding mom.
嗯  我努力之中
Well, I'm trying.
这一定很难  因为  在我们家
Yeah, well it must be hard, 'cause in my family,
我是黑人   我父母也是
I'm black, my parents are black.
我们一家都是    你知道我的意思吧?
We're all black. You know what I mean?
大概了解
I think so.
对了   你有看到这传单吗?
Oh! Did you see the flyer?
什麽传单?
What flyer?
艺术展
For the art show.
他的名字可显眼了
His name's really big.
你快一点  好吗?
Would you come on already?
同志文化中心?   这是怎麽回事?
Gay And Lesbian Center? When did this happen?
喔哦   你是说他没跟你…...
Oh, my god, you mean he didn't...
这些日子他不太都跟我说话
He doesn't tell me much these days.
别说是我说的
Oh, promise you won't tell him
不然他以後也不会跟我讲了
I told you or he'll stop telling me.
你不用大声喊   你第一次喊我就听到了
You don't have to yell,  I heard you the first time.
我不知道什麽时候会回家
And I don't know when I'll be back.
贾斯汀
Justin!
注意安全
Be careful.
克丽丝  帮我拿那铁槌
Chris, pass me that hammer.
你真的很厉害     谢谢
You're really good at that.  Thanks.
我喜欢你们的手链
I like you guys' bracelets.
喔  这是象徵我们的友谊
Oh, they're for friendship. I mean,
他不是我男朋友
He's not my boyfriend.
-我知道　　-你怎麽知道我是弯的?
-I figured.  －You can tell I'm gay?
你人在这儿  不是吗?
Well you're here, aren't you?
我到楼下餐厅  喝点汽水
I'm heading on down to the diner
你要不要一起去?
To get a soda. Do you want to come?
好
Sure.
你要干嘛?    她以为你是拉拉
What are you doing?  She thinks you're a lesbian.
我就不能假装一下吗?
Well, can't I be one of the cool people too?
你真是怪人
You're a freak.
你真的很有才华    真的吗?
You know, you have real talent.  Really?
你应该好好进修   也许去读艺术学校
You should develop it. Maybe go to art school.
我一直在想这件事
I've been thinking about that.
如果你需要推荐书
Well, if you ever need a recommendation.
谢谢你
Thanks.
你觉得布莱恩会来吗?
Do you think Brian's going to come?
别对他抱太大希望   好吗?
Don't expect too much from him, okay?
怎样是太大的希望？
What's too much?
什麽希望都别抱
Anything at all.
你还是有很多恋爱的机会    贾斯汀
You'll have lots of relationships, Justin,
跟很多有趣的人
With lots of interesting people.
我知道你现在不这麽想   但以後你会了解
I know you don't believe that right now, but you will.
我只是想要他来看　他当主角的那幅画被展示出来
I just want him to see his picture framed, that's all.
你确定要进去吗?
Are you sure you want to do this?
为什麽不?    进去看看你的世界
Yeah, why not? I'll get a taste of your world,
看我是从哪里 把你救出来
See what I'm saving you from.
跟我记忆中一样
Just the same as I remember it.
这里的人也一样
Even the guys look the same.
为何你不来这了呢?
Why'd you stop?
不合适我  而且我遇到一个人
It wasn't for me. And I met someone.
我们在一起快6年了
Yeah, we were together almost six years.
哇  谁提分手的?
Wow. So, who left who?
他去世了
He died.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事
Nobody's fault.
你好
Hi!
这就是久闻大名的帅哥理疗师?
So, is, uh... is this the famous chiropractor?
大卫   这是艾美特
David, this is Emmett.
-你好  艾美特　-你好  帅哥
-Hi, Emmett.　-Hello, gorgeous.
嗯  我...
So, um, so I've, um...
我背上的肌肉有点紧绷
I've got a little tightness right in here.
偏偏是不该紧的地方   能帮我按一下吗?
One place I don't need it. Would you mind?
可以啊  不过你得先预约
I wouldn't mind at all if you made an appointment.
嗯~值得一试
Well, it's worth a shot.
泰德在哪?
Where's Ted?
和面团宝宝出去玩了 (松饼公司的吉祥物)
Out with the Pillsbury doughboy.
老天  你看那个男的
Oh, my god. That guy over there
真像马修?麦康利  (肌肉男星)
Looks exactly like Matthew Mcconaughey.
也许他习惯裸体抽大麻呢    失陪了
Maybe he smokes pot naked. Excuse me.
他真是基情四射 是吧
Doesn't hold anything back, huh?
他这已经算低调了
He was toning it down for you.
你跑哪去了?
Where the fuck have you been?
布莱恩  这是大卫
Brian, this is David.
喔  妈的　新男友耶
Oh, fuck me, the new boo.
久闻大名
I've heard a lot about you.
我也是
And I've heard a lot about you too.
右边16分钟  左边11分钟
Sixteen right, eleven left.
-什麽?　　　-没事
-Excuse me?　-Nothing.
你发神经了    磕了什麽药?
You're tweaked, what are you on?
摇头丸、拉K、神仙水　芝麻街最常教的那些字母
Oh, e, k, ghb. Most of the letters on "Sesame Street."
你嗑了这麽多   你会脱水的
You're gonna get dehydrated taking all that shit.
我去帮你拿水
I'm gonna get you some water.
-喝啤酒吗  -好
- Want a beer? - Sure.
你可把他训练得真好
Well, you've got him well-trained.
他照顾我  我照顾他
Well, he takes care of me, and I take care of him.
嘿  大夫
So, doc...
你和每个病人都上床吗?
Do you fuck all of your patients?
如果你是指迈克
Well, if you're referring to Michael,
我们在一起前
I released him from my care.
我们就已经医好他了
Before we went out together.
你呢?   从事哪方面工作?
What about you? What do you do?
搞广告的
Advertising.
嗯~那你一定知道  怎麽搞别人
Well, you must know a thing or two about screwing people yourself.
我做梦的时候都能搞
Yeah, I could do it in my sleep.
我也相信你可以
I bet you could.
大卫 你知道吗
You know, Dave,
你和小迈约会最奇怪的地方吗?
What's weird about you meeting Mikey?
小迈?
"Mikey"?
我们通常都一起出动钓男人
Is that we usually meet guys together.
他们通常都被你钓回家了
And they usually end up with you.
只有最幸运的人才会
The lucky ones.
幸运？我很怀疑
Debatable.
我错过了什麽?
So what'd I miss?
没什麽特别的
Nothing special.
好的
Okay,
猜猜这首我最爱的歌剧是出自哪出剧?
Identify my favorite aria of all time
猜中的话   你就被加入我的最爱
And you instantly become my new favorite person.
谢谢你给我这麽大压力
Oh, well, thanks for not putting any pressure on me.
莫札特:《狄多王的仁慈》薛斯托咏唱曲 第二幕
"Clemenzo Di Tito", Sesto's Aria, act two.
拜托　出难一点的题目吧
Come on, give me a tough one.
哇~别让我这麽快为你着迷
Okay, stop trying to make me fall for you.
-我有吗? 　　　 -你是我在匹兹堡遇到第一个
-Who's trying?  -You are the first person I've met in Pittsburgh
知道薛斯托咏唱曲的人
who knows Sesto's Aria.
我应该是唯一知道的
I'm the only other person who knows.
你知道吗   我小时候
You know, when I was a kid,
周六下午时常装病
I used to pretend I was sick on Saturday Afternoons
然後溜出去
so I could skip literally.
听收音机里的梅特歌剧节目
And listen to the Met opera broadcasts on the radio.
我希望那时就认识你    我们就可以一起听了
Huh, I wish I'd known you. We could have listened together.
这样不算越界吧?
Is, uh, is this allowed?
不算吧
Yeah.
只是
Only, uh...
我还没有完全准备好
I'm not quite... ready yet.
没关系
It's okay.
我很快会调整好
But I will be soon.
而且
And, uh...
我觉得这将会是个很棒体验
I have a feeling it's going to be great.
我想你刚应该不太好受
You had a hideous time, I can tell.
我不介意偶尔出来放松一下
Ah, I don't mind going out once in a while.
你是在暗示我是个无乐不作的女王?
Are you implying that I'm a scene queen?
你是啊
You are a scene queen.
我们在匹兹堡   没什麽乐可作
We're in Pittsburgh, there is no scene.
那这里有什麽吸引人的?
Yeah, so what's the big attraction?
如果你不出来   就交不到朋友
Well, if you don't go out, you don't meet People.
那我呢?
What about me?
极少数的例外  而且我的朋友都在这...
Rare exception. Besides, my friends are here...
你的朋友?　　真是好朋友啊
Your friends? Some friends.
你朋友布莱恩刚才想勾引我
Your friend Brian tried to hit on me.
他不会那样
He did not.
我也曾被人这麽勾引过
I've been around the block.
他总是一副想勾引人的样子
He's always like that.
而且  他嗑了药  有点high
Besides, he was high.
我只是想让你知道
I'm just telling you.
他不会这样做的
He wouldn't.
他已经这样做了
He did.
可恶
Shit.
他抢不你走   你是我的
Well, he can't have you. You're mine.
我告诉你   我不去
I told you, I'm not going.
我向他保证你会去的
I promised him you'd be there.
你不应该给他那种我做不到的保证
Well, you should stop making promises that I can't keep.
别这麽机车   我在帮你擦屁股
Hey, don't be a shit. I'm trying to clean up some of your mess.
嘿  是他自己投怀送抱
Look, he's the one that threw himself at me.
我甩都甩不掉
I've been trying to get rid of him.
你可以去跟法官说
Tell it to the judge.
你何时说话变得像你家那位?
When did you start sounding like your girlfriend?
是时候你该为社群贡献一点
It's time you became part of the community.
听着  别因为我干男人
Look, just because I fuck guys
我就应该属於什麽社群
Does not mean I'm part of some community.
也不代表我和社群的人
And it doesn't mean I have anything in common
有任何共通之处
with someone else who does.
其实不只你认为的那样
You know, it's more than that.
我们必须互相照顾
we need to take care of each other.
我不想照顾别人
I don't need to take care of anyone,
我也不需要别人来照顾我
And I don't need anyone to take care of me.
有一天你会需要的
One day you might.
干他的团体
Fuck groups.
我以为你干过(团体)了
I thought you did.
偶尔会干　还非得有邀请函才能加入
Occasionally, but it's by invitation only.
你看到了吗?   你的画每幅标价美金一百元
Did you see this? they're charging $100
每一幅都是
For every one of your drawings.
你要发财了
You could be rich.
这是慈善活动   收入不是给我的
It's charity. I don't get to keep it.
还是很值得说嘴
Still.
你可以不要一直朝着大门看吗?
And would you stop watching the door?
他琴弹得很好  对吧
He plays beautifully, doesn't he?
我不太懂音乐
I'm all a-tingle.
所以你们两个干过了没?
So have you two had sex yet?
没有
No.
你小声点可以吗?
Would you keep your voice down?
那你们何时小声过了？
Well, when are you?
当我们两个都觉得应该做的时候
When we both know it's the right thing to do.
上床从来就不是应该做的事情
Sex is never the right thing to do.
救济穷人才是应该做的事情
Feeding the poor is the right thing to do.
聘雇残障人士才是应该做的事情
Hiring the handicapped is the right thing to do.
捐血才是应该做的事
Donating blood.
好吧   我了解你的意思
All right, all right, you made your point.
所有人都喜欢你的画
Everyone loves your drawings.
-你们要不要去吃些东西　　    -我不饿
-You guys check out the food?   -I'm not hungry.
好吧  那些帅哥怎麽样?
Okay. How about the cute guys?
那边也有一些和你年纪差不多的小帅哥
There's some right over there. Just about your age.
他来了
He's here.
开心哦
Mmm! yippee.
你不想去找他吗?
Well, aren't you going to go over there?
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming.
随便啦
Whatever.
这里有暗室吗?
Where's the back room?
琳赛   这是大卫
Lindsay, this is david.
-你好　　　　　　　-你好
-Nice to meet you.　-Nice to meet you.
嘿  迈克
Whoo! Michael.
我们先去看看阴道的雕刻吧　早看完早了事
Let's go check out the vagina sculptures first, get it over with.
有名的小画家啊
The famous "art-eest."
你看过我的画了吗?
Did you see my stuff?
不  我得先喝一杯
no, I had to get a drink first.
你感兴趣的话   可以到那里看看
It's over there, in case you're interested.
喂
Psst.
我觉得这位艺术家有点失真了
I think the artist has taken some liberties.
哦~画得非常拟真啊
Oh, that's a perfect likeness.
拜托…你的屌才没那麽大
Come on, it was never that big.
嘿～你可是很久没看过我的大屌了
Hey, you haven't seen it in a long time.
我也很久没看《乱世佳人》(电影)
I haven't seen "gone with the wind" in a long time either,
但我仍然知道它片长三个半小时
But i know it's still three and a half hours.
看看   布莱恩和迈克脱口秀
The brian and michael show.
blah~blah  没完没了的
Blah, blah, blah. stuck in perpetual reruns.
他们总是这样吗?  迈克跟在布莱恩後面追?
Is it always like that? Michael running after him?
相信我   这是史上最棒的爱情故事
It's the greatest love story never told, trust me.
-阁下大名? 　　　    -大卫
-Oh, what is your name?    -David.
-茉蕾妮      -相信我   大卫
-Melanie. 　-Trust me,  David,
就算你不在了　　迈克还是会跟在他後面
Long after you're gone, he'll still have Michael.
布莱恩可怜的小跟班
Brian's little acolyte, poor guy.
哦～不过别担心    就算迈克等一辈子
Oh, but don't worry. Michael can't wait forever.
布莱恩也不会干他的　　抱歉我讲粗话
Brian'll never fuck him. Pardon my french.
对了　听说你昨晚勾引大卫
By the way, I heard you hit on david last night.
我没那麽疯吧
I couldn't have been that high.
你有   你真的做了
You were. and you did.
我是在测试他
I was testing him.
我想看看　　他有机会的话　　会不会甩了你
I wanted to see if he'd drop you the first chance he got.
最好是
Oh, yeah right.
我不是都在照顾你吗?
Aren't I always looking out for you?
你只是在嫉妒终於有人
You're just jealous because somebody finally
认为我很性感或什麽的
thinks I'm hot or something.
你很性感或什麽的
You are hot or something.
你从14岁开始  我就一直跟你这样说了
I've been telling you that since you were 14.
但你偏不相信
But you won't believe me.
所以~　我只是迈克的备胎
So, I suppose I just keep him company while Michael waits.
该死
Oh! oh, shit!
哦~　原来你和迈克一起的
Oh, you're with Michael.
-对　　-天啊
-Yeah.  -Um, oh, jesus,
对不起   我刚不是那个意思
I-I'm sorry. I-I didn't mean that.
我是说   布莱恩总是喜欢
I-I mean-- well, I-I mean Brian's the one
跟新朋友炫耀自己情史
That's always showing up with some new guy,
所以我只是以为....
so I just assumed it that...um.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
事实上  他们~　他们~只是像好朋友一样爱着对方
Well, you know, they, they're-- they love each other as friends,
仅此而已   真的  只是这样
But that's it. That's really-- that's all it is.
是吗？ 我看起来不像
Really, it's not like I didn't know.
要不要吃个虾球?
Do you want a shrimp ball?
不了
No.
谢谢
Thanks.
这就是我所谓的一件..
Now that's what I call a piece.
艺术品　(piece後常接ass)
Of art.
我一直很欣赏有创造力的人
I've always admired creative people.
你是很有创造力的人  小妞
You're pretty creative yourself there, missy.
我不是
Not me.
但是迈克   他有天赋
But Michael, he's got a gift.
我不晓得他会画画
I didn't know he could draw.
他不会画画
Oh, he can't.
他小时候我帮他买过描图纸
I bought him tracing paper when he was a kid
这样他可以临摹漫画人物
so he could copy his comic books.
但他画的蜘蛛人总是
His spiderman always ended up with
更像孤儿安妮
Looking more like little orphan annie.
那他有什麽天赋?
Well, what's his talent?
他没有可以出名的技艺
Well, it's nothing he'd be famous for.
你不可能看到...
You won't ever see his...
他的画挂在画廊或者...
Paintings hanging in an art gallery or...
听到他在卡内基音乐厅演奏　(纽约着名的音乐厅)
Hear him playing at carnegie hall.
但是说到照顾别人
But when it comes to taking care of people
他比任何人更了解你的需求
Knowing what you need better even than you do
他也简直是个毕卡索
He's a fuckin' picasso.
光与影完美的交融
Beautiful light and shadow.
非常过目难忘
Very... haunting.
摄影者的视角……满独特的
The photographer has a great eye.
强烈的...  元素结合
Strong... composition.
你不能待在这里  你快回去吧
You can't stay, you have to leave.
贾斯汀   别太机车
Now, Justin, don't be mean.
我会遵守承诺的
I've kept my end of the bargain.
现在我只想看看我儿子的作品
Now-now I would like to see my son's work.
我不会让你感到尴尬的   我保证
I won't embarrasse you. I promise.
贾斯汀  这位是你母亲吗
Justin, is this your mother?
你好  我是詹妮弗
Hi, I'm Jennifer.
茉蕾妮    琳赛
Melanie.  Lindsay.
你的儿子真有才华
You know, your son's remarkably talented.
你应该为他感到骄傲
you should be very proud.
谢谢你  我的确为他感到骄傲
Well, thank you. I am.
好漂亮的孩子
And what a beautiful baby.
他叫盖斯    贾斯汀帮忙取的名字
His name's Gus. actually, Justin's the one who named him.
真的吗   那是他泰迪熊的名字
Really? well, that was his teddy bear's name.
哦~泰迪熊
Aw! oh, a teddy bear.
妈
Mom!
你是他妈妈吗?
Um, are you the mother?
对  但我们一起抚养他
Uh, yes, but we're raising him together.
这很好啊
Well, that's wonderful.
我以前从来没见过拉拉双亲
I've never met lesbian mothers before.
我是说  我看过你们...  他们
I mean, I-I read about you... them,
常在报纸上看到的
In the papers all the time.
总是有些阿拉巴马的法官
Yeah, seems like there's always some judge in Alabama
想夺走我们的孩子
trying to take our kid away.
所以我才要嫁给一个律师
That's why I married a lawyer.
你看过画了吗?
Have you seen the art?
还没
Not yet.
亲爱的    你的作品在哪里?
where's your stuff, honey?
她来支持你了　这才是最重要的
She came. That's huge.
巨大的能量
Tremendous energy.
真的朝你射出...
It really comes right out at you.
罗杰  我觉得我准备好了...
Roger... I think I'm ready.
我答应过要弹钢琴的
I promised to play the piano.
-你只是义工　　　　　-说的对   管他的
-You're just volunteering.   -you're right. fuck 'em!
你画的那个人是谁?
Who's that guy you drew?
对不起    没关系
Oh, sorry!  that's all right.
噢  对不起
Ouch! i'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
-我很抱歉　　　　　　-怎麽了?
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.　-What?
-我硬不起来　　　-怎麽了?
-No, I-I can't.　　-What is it?
-有问题吗?　　　　　　　-这样没办法
-Is something wrong?　-It just won't work.
我以为我可以的  真的
I thought I could do this. I really did.
我知道  你人很好  聪明又有才华
I mean, you are so nice and smart and talented.
钢琴弹得很好
And you play the piano beautifully.
-但是..  　-但是..
-But? 　-well..
继续   说出来吧
Go on, say it.
你不是我喜欢的类型
You're just not my type.
喜欢的类型?
Type?
你搞我吗?
Are you serious?
天啊   我不敢相信  在我们交心後?
God! I don't believe this. after all that?
我以为你不是只想要"性"的关系
I thought you didn't want sex to be everything.
是呀  可是...
Yeah, but...
我还是希望"性"是其中一部份...
I'd like it to be something.
你跟其他人都一样
You're just like all the others.
我袜子呢?
Where's my sock?
是我不对   对不起
Look, it's my fault, i admit it.
干   我不知道自己哪里不对劲
I mean, I-I don't know what the hell's wrong with me.
我是说  你很迷人
I mean, you're a catch.
任何一个异性恋女人  都会觉得你很有吸引力
Any straight woman would find you incredibly attractive.
你说这些是为了让我好过一点吗?    去你的
Oh, is that supposed to make me feel better? fuck you.
我知道我们在很多事情上都有共同点
Look, I know we share all the important things
音乐　幽默感
Music, a sense of humor.
这对我来说都觉得很合适
This would be a totally appropriate relationship for me.
唯一的问题就是 "性"方面不合适
The only problem is, is that sex isn't appropriate.
是我错了
You know, I was wrong.
你不是跟别人一样   你是比他们更糟
You're not like all the others, you're worse.
因为你以为知道
Because you think knowing sesto's aria
《狄多王的仁慈》薛斯托咏唱曲
from "clemenzo di tito"
就能让你高人一等
Somehow makes you better.
让我告诉你一件事
Well, let me tell you,
你不过是个傲娇屁精
You're nothing but a pretentious,
以自我为中心　无聊透顶的大屁精
self-involved, 　boring asshole.
成天跟底迪们鬼混
Who's still hanging around with younger guys
还指望他们跟你性交
Who don't want you and never will.
你太可悲了
You're pathetic!
那你呢?
And what about you?
在你指挥完第501场桑德海姆音乐会
You know, after you conduct your 501st tribute to Sondheim,
你就应该去躺健身房
You might try going to a gym.
至少去看看跑步机长什麽样子
You know, get on a treadmill for once in your life.
还有  冲一冲你的嘴
And do something about your breath!
我想说的是
Listen.
我想我们连朋友都做不了
I don't suppose we could still be friends.
所以我想　"好吧　至少他正在经历一些事"
So I thought, "okay, he's having... experiences."
但是好歹也该和同年龄的人吧
But with boys his own age.
这个　男人  肯定有30多了吧
This... man, he must be in his thirties.
啊  还不到
Well not yet,
但是我很高兴让他知道你这麽觉得
But I'll be happy to tell him you thought so.
一切都是不对劲
Well it's not right.
但它发生了
It happens.
如果他爸爸发现了
If his father finds out--
跟我说说这个男人　这位...老兄
Tell me about him, this... person.
我得多知道一些
I have to know.
布莱恩?肯尼
Brian Kinney.
上帝赐予同志圈的大礼
God's gift to gay p.a.
每个人都想要布莱恩
They all want Brian.
好消息是　　没人可以拥有他
But the good news is, no one can have him.
他搞过他们　伤了他们的心
He screws them,  breaks their heart
然後他们就长大成熟了
and they wise up.
大部份人都这样
Well, most of them anyway.
所以说  这个  呃...
So, this, uh...
布莱恩?肯尼
Brian Kinney...
他会伤我儿子的心
He's going to hurt my son.
-我该怎麽做?　　-什麽也不能做
-What do I do?   -Nothing.
你帮不上忙   除非你想火上加油
There's nothing you can do without making it worse.
他才17岁啊
He's only 17.
你第一次是几岁?
How old were you the first time?
-16　　　　　-我15
-Sixteen.　　-Fifteen.
总之   如果能让你觉得好一点
Anyway, if it makes you feel any better,
我认识布莱恩的时候他才14岁
I've known Brian since he was 14.
他没什麽大变化
He hasn't changed much.
我觉得   他和贾斯汀 还挺相配的
In fact, I'd say he and Justin are pretty evenly matched.
我不知道是否真的可以这麽包容
I don't know if I can be so accepting.
亲爱的
Honey.
詹妮弗
Jennifer.
你也没什麽选择
You don't have too much choice.
你能做的就是   希望他们能小心而安全
All you can do is hope that they'll be careful,
而且还记得你的电话号码
And that they remember your phone number.
-来　　　　-你敢
-Here.　-Don't you dare.
我请客
This is on me.
谢啦
Thanks.
噢   这个
Oh, here.
给他需要的
Give him what he needs.
承认吧   你怀念这一切
Admit it! You missed all this.
怀念你们这些   自恋狂
The rampant narcissism,
卑鄙小人和毒虫?
The sleaze, the drug use?
我才不想念这些
I don't think so.
那你为什麽回来?
So why'd you come back?
等我搞清楚    我再告诉你
When I figure it out, I'll let you know.
哇  你们看
Oh, look,
《超人集中营》的演员来了　(都是童星演出的影集)
It's the cast of "ZOOM".
我们来这庆祝
We're celebrating.
贾斯汀今天卖了一些他的画作
Justin sold some of his art today.
包括你那一张    正面全裸的
The one of you, naked.
谁会买那幅画?
Who'd buy that?
可能是某个一直想被你拖去行房的娘娘
Probably some desperate queen who's always pined for you.
泰德　　你真是体贴啊
Oh, Ted. how thoughtful.
啊  天啊   我好喜欢这首歌
Oh, my god, I used to love this song!
来跳舞吧
Then, let's dance.
我要去尿尿
I gotta pee.
来吧  大卫太医
Okay, Dr. feel good.
让我看看你的舞姿   来嘛
Let me see you shake your groove thang. Come on.
看看~他会跳舞耶　果然是同志无误
Ooh, he can dance. he is gay, after all.
有人说过你是最不良示范吗？
Anybody ever tell you you're a bad influence?
你...
you are
噢  你好吗?
Hi. how you doing?
多好了　所以不谢过了
Better. no thanks to you.
我一直不清楚那天晚上到底发生什麽事
I never really knew for sure what happened that night.
我想你应该已经恢复了
So, uh, I figured you came out of it Okay.
我很怕从报纸看到你的讣闻
I kept looking the papers.
是喔   那还真是...　贴心
Gee, that's... really thoughtful.
我  呃...
I, uh...
那天我叫了救护车之後
Waited on the corner...
在转角一直等...  确定他们真的上去了
After I called the paramedics, to make sure they came.
是你叫的救护车
You mean you called 9-1-1?
我不想留在旁边
I didn't want to stick around.
我很害怕   怕被发现毒品 然後进了警局
I was afraid, you know, the drugs and shit.
是喔
Right.
你喝了那麽大一口   我心想...  糟糕.)
I mean, you took so much, I was like, "whoa".
不管怎样    我很高兴你没事
Anyway... I'm glad you're okay.
那麽...
Well, uh...
或许我们可以  找时间再聚一聚
Maybe we could, uh, get together again some time.
这次不叫救护车
Without the paramedics.
你在这     怎麽那麽久?
There you are. What's taking you so long?
在跟别人讲话啦
Just talking to some guy.
你叫什麽名字?
What's your name again?
-泰德    -泰德  就是泰德
-Ted.    -Ted, right.
嗯   再见了
Yeah, I'll... see you later.
再见
See ya.
嗨   你好
Hey, how's it going?
嘿    你好吗?
Yo!   Hi, how are you?
嘿  你...
Hi! hey, how are
你好吗?
Hey, how's it going?
你的项链不错看喔
It's a great little collar that you got.
嗨    你好
As if.  How's it going?
你们两个真的在一起    真了不起
You two are together, that's something.
噢  天哪  你在厕所跟某个小男生做了吧
Oh, my god, you did it in the little boys' room.
没有
Nope.
你要了谁的电话吗?
You got somebody's phone number?
每个人都拒绝我...
I was rejected by everybody.
回来的感觉真好
It's good to be back!
-来杯鸡尾酒吧　　　　-好啊
-Let's get you a cocktail.　-Okay.
嗨～　猛男   想跳舞吗?
Hey, hot stuff, you want to dance?
不太想
I don't think so.
那你想干嘛?
Well, what do you want to do?
带你回家
Take you home.
我是阿斯特罗队长
Captain Astro.
你在想谁?
Who are you thinking about?
什麽?
What?
你闭上眼睛的时候　你在想谁?
When you close your eyes, who are you thinking about?
(男的是本集一开始的漫画店店员)
9fcfc77f322e4e3d9d8ba4165feb6e73